Nermin Memovic

Frontend & Wordpress Developer

CONTACT

+38166100751

Belgrade

nermin.memovic990@gmail.com

in Linkedin

Linkoun

Portfolio

 $X \times$

(Github

SKILLS

HTML CSS SCSS/SASS

PHP JavaScript

aScript (jQuery

Wordpress ACF Plugin

CPT Ajax

GSAP Typ

CF7 Plugin

Typed.js) (SEO

Elementor

Boostrap 5 (

) (Git

(Figma)

Linear)

Click Up

EDUCATION

Fakultet Tehnickih Nauka, Kosovska Mitrovica - Master's Degree

Environmental engineering
2017 - 2020

Fakultet Tehnickih Nauka, Kosovska Mitrovica -Bachelor's Degree

Environmental engineering

2009 - 2017

HOBBIES

I have been playing guitar and bass guitar for nearly twenty years, with bass being my primary instrument. I had a band with which I performed at almost all major festivals in the country and the region. Although I'm not as active in music anymore, it still plays a significant role in my life. I believe that frontend development allows me to best express my artistic freedom, which greatly influenced my career choice and is what attracts me most to the job, as it allows me to combine creativity with technical skills.

PROFILE

I'm a Web Developer with three years of experience. I specialize in creating websites in WordPress, developing custom themes, using technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP. I mainly focus on front-end development, and I plan to further improve my skills by learning React. I work well in teams but am also prepared for independent work.

EXPERIENCE

JV Dev Center

2024 - Present

Wordpress Developer

Collaborate with the JV Dev Center team to manage all aspects of website development, including design, frontend, backend, responsiveness, and deployment. Primarily work with WordPress themes and Elementor to create tailored solutions.

Bureau TwentyTwo

2021 - 2024

Web Developer

As a web developer, my main responsibility was working on the development of frontend technologies like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Over the past year, I frequently transitioned into backend development, using PHP, which allowed me to gain broader experience in creating complete web solutions. I developed websites using custom themes, writing the entire code from scratch. In close collaboration with designers, I created pixel-perfect websites, ensuring responsiveness and SEO optimization, delivering both technically and visually optimized projects.

PROJECTS

Bureau TwentyTwo

Open Link

The agency specializing in design, branding, and development requested a redesign of its existing website. In close collaboration with designers, I was responsible for the complete development, including frontend (creating pages, custom post types, animations, and responsiveness), as well as the entire backend and deployment on the existing hosting.

The Daily Muck

<u>Open Link</u>

A news portal required a WordPress solution tailored to their business with a custom design. In collaboration with designers, I was responsible for the entire development, covering all aspects of the frontend as well as the complete backend.

3AP

Open Link

The company, which specializes in software solutions and business process digitalization, needed to transition to a WordPress site. During this project, I was responsible for all aspects, including frontend, animations, responsiveness, SEO optimization, and backend.

Plants By Number

Open Link

A company that specializes in selling plants online needed a new WordPress solution for its business. On this project, I was responsible for developing the frontend solutions.

Executive Assistants

Open Link

The "Executive Assistance" website focuses on offering recruitment services tailored specifically for executive and administrative assistants. I played a key role in this project by managing the entire frontend development process.

Seawall Point

<u>Open Link</u>

A company specializing in luxury vacation properties needed an online solution for its business. My role on this project was to develop the complete frontend solution, including animations and responsiveness.